Watch how these HBCU students treat these MAGA folks running up on their campus at TSU.
MAGA supporters invaded our HBCU.
Y'all, what is going on over here?
You called the East primitive for what?
We created y'all knowledge.
We created y'all science.
We created y'all math.
Y'all didn't do besides steal.
Y'all didn't do anything to your...
You guys didn't make your...
You guys touch children.
Wrap it up.
Showing them the door.
Deuces.
We're walking them to the door, y'all.
Get to step.
I don't even know how they got on campus.
We're going to figure that out, but I don't know.
They need to get like a trespass penalty or something because...
Sending them off.
Tell him it's that boy.
He thought he was going to come up like Charlie.
Yes.
Say good job, TSU.
Good job.
Get under my...
Incredible job, TSU.
Because they, believing their own lies, thought they was going to run up in your school and
that you was going to battle them with their violence and their BS.
And y'all said, we at school.
We're going to battle you with knowledge.
Now, for the black cops that was there helping them, that's another conversation for another
time.
However, in this conversation, I just want to big y'all up.
Because you said, get out of our school because we are getting in these blocks.
Support a real one.
Here you go.
The other one.
It's not necessary.
The other person has been actually telling you to better understand.